JAZIEL ENRIQUEZ (JAZZ)

Contact info:

Email: jazielenriquez@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jazielenriquez/

Online Portfolio: https://jenriquezportfolio.netlify.app/

Phone: 915-888-5233

PROFILE SUMMARY

Proficient in problem solving and troubleshooting hardware and software. Effective at simplifying technical terms into simple terms. Excellent knowledge in computer hardware. Experience with ticketing systems. Understand PC/LAN hardware troubleshooting. Proficient knowledge of Mac OS, Windows OS, Office 365, and networking. Strong knowledge of TCP/IP.

BA in Psychology. Bilingual (Spanish). Customer service and sales experience. Extraordinary with guest interaction. Excellent organizational, time management, and people skills. Self starter, critical thinker, and excellent at interpersonal/communication skills. Self learner and empathetic towards others.

CERTIFICATIONS/PROJECTS

Tech Certifications

Google IT Support Professional Certificate – a six month IT support program that covers troubleshooting, customer service, networking, operating systems, system administration, and security, and includes hands-on labs.

CompTIA A+ - In progress

Online Portfolio

Personalized HTML, CSS, and Javascript code to create a simple yet modern portfolio during my free time.

Link: https://jenriquezportfolio.netlify.app/

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

COMPUTER TECHNICIAN - SMS INFOCOMM 2023 - PRESENT

Responsibilities:

Organized and categorized personal duties to complete business daily goals.

Took apart and re-assembled computers.

Resolved hardware and software issues by using problem solving skills.

Manually set up computer systems and hardware and installed/re-install software for computer users.

Used troubleshooting skills to determine root cause of problem.

Input data into ticket system to keep track of problems.

Effectively communicated to customer via system what was done to their hardware/software and what troubleshooting and solutions steps were taken.

EDUCATOR - LULULEMON - 2022-2023

Responsibilities:

Used problem solving skills by assisting customers with their needs in person and on the phone.

Resolved and helped co-workers by troubleshooting technical issues with POS system, Windows software, and mobile devices.

Communicated and developed relationships effectively with all my co-workers by using interpersonal, teamwork, and leadership skills

Adapted independently and used problem solving skills when encountering problems.

Took initiative to greet, know, and help the customers.

Adapted to any role that was asked of me to do and asked questions if needed in order to perform my task better.

Maintained a positive, encouraging, and friendly attitude.

Contributed to revenue increase each month by increasing item per transaction sales.

HOSPITALITY TEAM MEMBER - CHICK-FIL-A - 2020-2022

Responsibilities:

Provided and maintained high-standard customer service in a fast-paced environment.

Mastered teamwork, customer service, and communication by doing my assigned tasks.

Communicated clearly with customers and co-workers and maintained a positive, friendly, and welcoming attitude.

Resolved complaints quickly, professionally, and kindly.

Adapted to different roles in my position quickly and effectively.

Used problem solving skills to assist customer's needs.

Maintained an optimistic and customer first mentality.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS AT EL PASO – BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN PSYCHOLOGY, 2022

COMMUNITY SERVICE

Shoreline City, Dallas, TX 2023

Responsibilities: Created a loving atmosphere with excitement and fun for people. In charge of leading, encouraging, and greeting others. Had a passionate, authentic, and friendly mindset to build genuine relationships. Maintained extraordinary guest interaction, organizational, and time management skills.